First rule, you get 12 hours.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing.
Just stick to the script, all right?
Third.
I know, past and future.
Must remain untouched.
Got it.
Seriously, that's the hundredth time.
Let's gear up.
Dive.
It didn't take too long to realize
Something has changed in the back of my mind
Your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was
When the flash froze everything before
Without you
I don't know if I could take this road
And I'm about to lose my mind
Every minute that I die back in time
Every single existence rewinds
Something secretive hidden inside
Dry all night
All the hottest and the smiles never faded
I know you'll be by my side
When we make it
Come back from the times
Back in time
Dive back in time
SOT
Guess who?
Great, if it isn't our landlady.
Just leave the picture on the counter and go.
That's the welcome I get?
Don't forget I'm letting you pay your debt off slowly.
And yet, you're here on your butt playing around.
You want to go out of business and get kicked out?
I grew up in this place with my parents.
I won't go anywhere until they come back.
Try to kick me out, and I'll hang myself right here.
Your dad'll never get a new tenant after that.
You wouldn't!
Idiot.
What did he call me?
Well…
I'll take the picture now, please, Choling.
Aye-aye, good boy!
Wait, good boy?
Did you bring the puppy a treat too?
You may be younger, but he's way more mature than you!
Right, so…
Dumb.
The only reason I put up with that moron is for your sake, you know.
Now, let's discuss the mission.
You're to grab financial data from Tredi Games before their third quarter report is released the day after tomorrow.
Problem is, the CEO is the only person with access.
He's scared of hackers, so he carries the data with him instead of leaving it on his computer.
Hackers, huh?
Great!
He's paranoid, so…
We should pass on this one!
The key is…
Emma.
As his assistant, she could peek at the numbers.
Promising.
And we've got a recent photo of her?
Sort of.
This is from her moments account.
It should be a good starting point.
Oh, late night snack.
There are other pictures as well.
If this doesn't help, go through her posts.
Maybe try last week?
We need the most recent numbers though.
We need to see the numbers.
Emma.
As his assistant, she could peek at the numbers.
Promising.
And we've got a recent photo of her?
Sort of.
This is from her moments account.
It should be a good starting point.
Oh, late night snack.
There are other pictures as well.
If this doesn't help, go through her posts.
Maybe try last week?
We need the most recent numbers though.
See something?
Yes.
But we've only got one shot.
First rule, you get 12 hours.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing.
Just stick to the script.
Alright?
Third.
I know.
Past and future.
Must remain untouched.
Got it.
Seriously.
That's the hundredth time.
I'll jump into the photo, and then you'll be my guide.
Let's gear up.
Hm.
Dive.
Stop.
Do as I say, and don't make this weird.
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
I'm listening.
While I'm here, think I'll test out these spring rolls.
Not yet.
Can't I at least enjoy the takeout?
Emma?
Come here.
Yeah.
One sec.
Hey.
That man is your boss.
Sure, Mr. Ju.
Be there in a jiffy.
How's that?
Good, right?
Such a proper assistant.
Uh, Emma?
Something bothering you?
Nothing much.
Just thinking about how the man in my life is the worst.
Moron.
You know not to add anything.
One lie inevitably leads to more.
Oh?
Did you get a boyfriend?
Uh, good question.
Do I have one?
You don't.
Now try to stay on track.
No, sir.
So, um, were you needing something from me, or?
I saw your post on Moments.
Sad takeout again.
You and I could grab a snack.
Oh, that's nice, but no thank you.
I specially ordered this food.
Why don't you call it a night and head home early?
And leave you here alone?
I'll keep you company.
Wouldn't you like that?
Uh, I don't know.
Our co-workers would talk.
You've been here almost two years.
We're like partners.
Don't you feel that way?
Uh, I think I should be getting back to my desk.
What do you want me to do?
Say it.
Lou?
What the hell's going on here?
They could've warned me this might happen.
You're fine. Go with this.
We shouldn't. We're at work.
This better not fail.
Mr. Xu, please don't. We're at work.
Lighten up. My office is the most private place in the building.
My PC and phone are both encrypted. No spyware.
Besides, I won't need photographs to remember this.
Put your pretty little head at ease.
Damn it, Lou.
You never said this was going to be part of the plan.
It's the only way to complete the mission.
You're kidding me.
If you make one change, it could end up causing a ripple effect.
The whole timeline could be disrupted.
I'll keep you up a bit.
Now's your chance! Push him!
Sorry, I need an... answer.
You saved my skin just now, Auntie.
Auntie? Is this the wrong daughter?
Oh, Mom! Hi!
It's your son, uh, I mean, daughter.
The worst freaking timing. Thanks a lot, Hag.
No, things are fine. Promise.
I saw the picture on Moments. Dinner so late?
No, no. I snapped that picture earlier.
And then I just forgot to post it until I got home.
Don't lie. You're working overtime again.
Living off fast food.
You know it's bad for you. You'll end up sick.
Mom, it's the 21st century. Fast food's pretty gourmet these days.
The ingredients are nice and... fresh.
You're just telling yourself that to justify the poison you're putting into your...
That's enough. Cut her some slack.
Let the poor girl finish work so she can go home.
By the way, honey, I know I suggested you block your mom on Moments.
So why'd you block me instead?
Oh, uh, that was an accident.
Your mom won't be so fussy if she doesn't see pictures like that.
It's late. Talk to your boss.
You should see if you can finish your work up in the morning.
Oh, and make time to find yourself a boyfriend. Okay?
Dad, I...
Why isn't your computer on?
Materials for tomorrow's meeting must be finished tonight.
All right. I'll let you go. Can't get you in more trouble.
Don't work too hard.
Right.
Good night.
Bye for now.
Don't forget. The meeting room needs to be cleaned and set up by 9am.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
And take out any trash before you leave.
Yep. On top of it, sir.
Dodged a bullet with him. What should I do next?
You heard the man. There's work to be done.
I'll help. Though you have to finish before 2 o'clock.
If you don't hurry, the timeline will change.
And we wouldn't want that, now would we?
I hate you. Truly.
Don't take your anger out on me.
Tell me.
Is this what her life is like every day?
Don't ask that.
Stay focused.
Tomorrow has to go well.
The only chance we have of getting info for the client is at that morning meeting.
Oh, right. I'm supposed to clean up.
You must get the data before 10am.
I'll guide you.
Just make sure you're ready to move.
Who's texting? It's late.
Better to not look.
So sleepy.
Careful, it's hot. Let them cool.
Don't be so hasty.
Sometimes the best course of action is to go slow.
Here.
So why did you pick it up, Daddy?
Your old man's got tough skin.
Please, stop pretending.
He's just putting on a show so you won't get hurt.
See, his fingers are red.
Okay, okay, no need to fuss over me.
You forget I'm a big strong man.
Now, go and grab me a bottle of wine.
I'm busy with the soup.
Why can't you get it yourself?
Please...
Hey, Dad...
Mom?
You're up.
I dreamt I was eating spring rolls with my parents.
Folks on your mind?
Yeah, and they're on hers as well.
When you became her,
you took on some of her feelings and memories
and must be tough.
I wonder if they'll come back.
It'll work out. Just rest.
Thanks.
Good night.
Darling, are you home yet?
Your father told me you got into some kind of trouble with your boss
because I called earlier.
I'm so sorry.
It's just that I worry about whether you're eating well
and getting enough sleep.
That's what moms are for.
You know you mean everything to us, right?
Deadly breathes.
Lead them out of their heart
and untide them together.
Deadly breathes.
Redly breathes.
Huh, excellent work.
Still in character?
Yeah, let's just make sure we pull this one off for the landlady,
because this gig is such hot carpet.
What was that?
You know, plenty of people would kill for a position like yours.
No, Mr. Zhu.
I wasn't complaining about work.
My sink's been acting up at home.
That's all.
Just do your job and talk less.
That's the only way to be a phoenix instead of a sparrow.
All right, let's begin.
Uh, hello?
What should I do?
Bide your time.
We're waiting for someone.
Talk about paranoid.
There's even privacy film on his laptop.
Don't let worry get the best of you now.
Take a deep breath and focus.
Stay calm.
At least give me a timeline.
It's a secret.
Damn you.
It's time.
Huh?
The glass!
Yes?
Oh no!
Oh!
Don't sit there.
What?
Help him clean his pants.
Sorry, sir.
Let me get that for you.
Stop!
I can handle it myself!
You pig!
Caught in the act!
Huh, gotcha.
No wonder you work so late.
You have a little skank taking care of you!
It's not what you think.
She's just my assistant.
Just where the hell were you putting your hands?
Is that what your job entails?
She's always flirting with me.
You only wanna...
Quite.
Loser voice.
I didn't do anything.
I know what your type is like.
Always after a big fish to reel in.
Bet your parents were worthless as well.
Those morons didn't teach you how to act.
The world would be better if they'd never had you.
Calm down.
Deep breaths.
Don't ruin this.
Remember, you have to stick to our rules no matter what.
First rule, you get 12 hours.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing.
Just stick to the script.
All right?
Third.
I know.
Past and future.
Must remain untouched.
Need another?
Enough.
Please.
We've acquired the data.
Mission complete.
Yesterday, Chia De Games was called out for fraudulent financial data.
A Mr. Zhu and Ms. Hu were arrested.
You still mad at me?
They deserve what they got. Things worked out fine.
Although, if I did change something, how many lives would be affected?
You were his assistant, Emma. This looks bad for you, too.
You won't find a job in this field again.
Try to learn new skills while you're still young.
No way.
I just...
You live strictly now
Where are you?
You make me stop now
Couldn't wait right here
Till you get there
We still have something lost in the darkness
To save you
Dad, Mom, I miss you
Tell me you aren't stupid
Hi
Mom, sweetie, are you crying?
Honey, I told you not to butt in
We've caused her enough problems
Apologies, your mother saw you missed her
She got excited and wanted to surprise you with some homemade spring rolls
Then she figured you could use a new blanket since it's cold
And thick winter clothes, too
I told her you could get all that in the city
But she insisted things bought with love are warmer
Hope you like them
If they're not stylish enough, wear them at home
Or donate them if you want to
Please, don't go!
Can't you stay a little while longer?
We don't want to interfere with your work
What's wrong?
Someone bullying you?
Just don't leave!
I'll meet you at the station
How's Emma doing?
I gotta admit, I'm kinda curious
Oh, sorry, sir
You're good
If you're running late to the train station
I could drive you there
I've told you
Never ask that
Yeah, I know
Just kidding
Hey boys, where are you?
Well, if it isn't my favorite landlady
A new case already?
You need a filter
Don't pitch us everything
Now a tragic story
A female corpse was found in the river last night
According to the police
The deceased was employed in the financial department of Chida Games before her death
Given the company's recent disgrace
Suicide has not been ruled out
We'll continue our coverage shortly
Yeah, coming
Coming
What's right for a nice swing?
What you can use to use?
Yeah
Let girl
floating around is the heartbeat of my chest
from 층 MOREN
the current director of any one
I'm Supreme
so I can't wait
from the inner Josh
to the other day
I never make an answer
with your hand
on the sides of your head
moving i need you
rator
in support
I am still
ainda
on that
you canimit
so i could
got lost in this street
i feel like i am living in
or maybe i should just
quit overthinking
I
once
that Mesd golpe
forex
no
my face
I
want
false
ago
I don't know how to take my eyes.
You should really stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it. Stop stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
You're a real life.
The dream of the dream is a dream.
What do you need to do to do?
So stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it. Stop stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
I understand how many of the problems are.
As for everyone's fault.
Stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
Yeah.
You